# 大家好 今天摘點菜葉子去餵小 餵那個小兔子
Hi everyone! Today I'm gonna get some veggie leaves for the lit, for the little bunnies.
# 這個菜葉子很嫩的哦
These veggie leaves are really young and tender you know.
# 這些菜葉子很靚我哦
These veggie leaves are really beautiful.
# 一片片來
Pick them out,
# 摘下來
piece by piece,
# 你看 這個
Look! This one,
# 這個 這個爆掉啦
this one, this one has already cracked open.
# 你看 這個爆掉了也可以
Look! This cracked one is still good.
# 很好吃的
It's really tasty.
# 今天沒帶刀
I don't have a knife with me today.
# 你看 這些菜葉子
Look! These veggie leaves...
# 這一大片都是兄弟家的哦 通通送給我們啦
This whole area belongs to my buddy. And he gives them all to us.
# 他說不要啦 他自己 他自己到外面去上班啦
He said he doesn't want it anymore. He, he's already got a job outside.
# 種了那麼多菜 那麼多包菜
Here are so many veggies, so many cabbages.
# 摘到摘不完 吃都吃不完
There's no way to pick them all, no way to finish them.
# 前兩天我們都扛了三四袋 三四袋那個牛皮袋呀
We've already taken three or four, three or four bags of cabbages a couple of days ago.
# 拿到村里面 讓他們想要的人就去拿
We took the cabbages back to the village. Anyone who needs them can take some.
# 每個人拿了幾個 幾個 一下就沒有啦
Everybody took a few, a few, and all were gone in a second.
# 過兩天吃完啦 我又來割一點 全部發給他們
When they have finished, I'll come again in a couple of days. All will be distributed to the villagers.
# 你看 這 半個牛皮袋
Look! Here, half a bag.
# 夠啦 夠兔子吃個 一個禮拜左右
It's enough, enough for the bunnies for, for about a week.
# 不要摘那麼多 下次來摘
Don't take too much. We'll come again next time,
# 才新鮮
to ensure the freshness.